AMIRHOSSEIN GOODARZI

REACT DEVELOPER

https://Amirhosseingoodarzi.vercel.app
https://www.linkedin.com/in/amir-hossein-goodarzi

Contact Info

(2) +98 9056325077 +98 9167943707

Amirgoodarzi.web@gmail.com

Tehran, Iran



ABOUT ME

I am a passionate and creative frontend developer with four years of experience in building user-friendly and responsive web applications using React.js. I have a solid understanding of web development fundamentals. I also have some exposure to backend development using Node.js and Express, which enables me to collaborate effectively with backend developers and integrate frontend and backend functionalities. I am always eager to learn new skills and technologies, and currently I am exploring Python and machine learning concepts to enhance my professional growth and expand my horizons.

EXPERIENCES

Mid-Level FrontEnd Developer 2021 - Now

- · Kahkeshan Group of Companies
- Collaborating with talented people.
- Create web products for both business and consumer use.

Junior FrontEnd Developer 2019-2021

- Freelancer
- Creating successful responsive websites that are fast, easy to use, and built with best practices.

Meta | Soci

2022

CERTIFICATES

• Meta | Social Metaverse Company

React & FrontEnd Developer

React is

2018

• Tehran, Sharif university of technology

Javascript Algorithms & Responsive Design

2022

FreeCodeCamp

Front-End Developer 2018

• University of Tehran

EDUCATION

Master of Software Engineering 2021 - 2023

Bachelor of Computer Engineering 2017 - 2020

FRONTEND SKILLS

Basic of Internet HTML5 **SEO Basics** CSS3 Responsive Design **BEM Architecture** SASS TailwindCss Bootstrap Chakra UI Javascript EcmaScript React React-router-dom Redux Thunk Toolkit React-Query Zustand Nextjs SSR & SSG

MOBILE SKILLS

React Native	
Expo	
CLI	
react-native-paper	
@rneui	

BACKEND FAMILIARITIES

Nodejs
Express
Schema and modelling Data
MVC Architecture
Security
Authentication & Authorization JWT Error Handling
Database
MongoDB
SQL
SHARED SKILLS

Version Control		
OOP		
Typescript		

GIT	
Github	

Package Manager	
Gitlab	
3111100	

YARN	
NPM	

Connections
Restfull Api
Axios
Documentation and swagger

Postman & Insomnia

Socket.io and SignalR

PORTFOLIOS

DDSS

- A large project including seven panels for safe transfer of files in organizations
- Introduced in Gitex 2023 Dubai

Defacement

 Monitoring and Logging defaced data around the world

Dana intel, Panel.danaintel

• A project to manage your organization risks

InspectionService

 A project consisting of **four dashboards** to manage processes between employers, suppliers and customers of a private company

GRE & IELTS Exam

• A great project to take exams like Cambridge tests.

Massanger

· Real-time chat with friend

Kahkeshan Groups of Companies

• A website to introduce our companies

Playkon

• A mobile app for listening to music online

Sanjify

• Maybe the best online test application in Iran:)

KNSMS Forwarder

 A mobile application to send incoming SMS to the email address as requested by the employer.

Nama Pardaz Company

 A project consisting of three dashboards to manage processes between employers, suppliers and customers of a private company

Danawan

 A native solution for easy migration from legacy WAN networks to a modern and secure network, using SDWAN and SASE concepts to increase bandwidth, centralized management, automation, full visibility, and network security.



PNUChapterSelection

A small project to choose chapters and articles on university

NeoGame Telegram bot

 A telegram bot to advert and sell game events, tokens, etc.

Stock exchange robot

· A Chrome extention to submit request

iliatek

 wAN online shop for healthcare products

Your Project:)

 A free space to have a fantastic website just for you:)